(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Peafowl of the Blue Flame
Pavolia Reine Birthday 2025
GUESTS + ANNOUNCEMENT!
Quack!
Peafowl of the Blue Flame
ANYA MELFISSA
KOBO KANAERU
MOONA HOSHINOVA
KUREIJI OLLIE
TSUNOMAKI WATAME
TAKANASHI KIARA
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
IIDA POCHI.
KiLLKiSS
Lyrics: Diggy-MO' / Music: 渡辺剛 (SUPA LOVE), Diggy-MO'
Lyrics: Diggy-MO' / Music: Tsuyoshi Watanabe (SUPA LOVE), Diggy-MO'
弄られて垂れ流す
Toyed with, letting it flow
音のない音は招く
Soundless sounds beckon
名前を捨てたのね あなたのモザイク
You've abandoned your name, haven't you? Your mosaic
が泣いている
is crying
can not, can not, not, not, no deny
紛れもなく真実
Undeniably the truth
さあ預けて
Come, entrust it
回帰するように
As if returning
エネルギーはサイクル そういまは
Energy is a cycle, yes, right now
無重力 象徴的なパレード
Zero gravity, a symbolic parade
この月夜に 仰げば仰げ
On this moonlit night, if you look up, look up
completeness
鳴呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, holding high the light of life
KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to
欺いて
Deceive me
KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to jud...
抱きしめて
Hold me close
ねぇ無防備だね
Hey, you're defenseless
美しい戯れに
In beautiful play
人は壊れてゆく
People are breaking
謳歌し割れ
Celebrate and break
'cuz we're all alone
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even when you bite down
手を挙げ 希え
Raise your hand and wish
oh when you bleed 惑星に沿う その影を伸ばせ
oh when you bleed, follow the planet, extend that shadow
ねえ私の世界が知りたがっているわさ
Hey, my world is wanting to know
you bleed yes bleed その血で
you bleed yes bleed with that blood
天の五線譜を書き換えれば
If you rewrite the staff of heaven
code 'KiLLKiSS' uh...
KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to judy...
欺いて
Deceive me
KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to KiLLKiSS to jude...
抱きしめて
Hold me close
醜い終局に
To the ugly end
すべてが変わってゆく
Everything is changing
儚いのね
It's fleeting, isn't it
そう このまま
Yes, like this
壊れて
Break
La la la la la, la la...
CR詠ZY
Lyrics, Music: 梅とら
Lyrics, Music: Umetora
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY 細胞レベル
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY Cellular level
あるに不本意 現状触れてる
Unwillingly in existence, touching reality
姿 仕草 滑稽でしょう
Appearance, gestures, it's comical, isn't it?
DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
I'M SO LAZY 多分そう
I'M SO LAZY Probably so
FINE SOUND 並べてるだけの人
FINE SOUND Just a person lining things up
TRASH TRASH TOSS AWAY
DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
IN THIS WORLD この頭には
IN THIS WORLD In this head
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL 舞い散る花びら
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL Dancing flower petals
パラライカ 飲みたいな
Paralyka, I want to drink it
La la la la la, la la...
誰もが抱いたい
Everyone wants to embrace
C-R-詠-Z-Y
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
On a momentary emotion RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
心は 95
Heart is 95
狂気のサムライ
Mad Samurai
血走らせた目で 引くくらい Ready to die
With bloodshot eyes, enough to back off, Ready to die
陽は昇り あなたの空 真っ黒な空
The sun rises, your sky, pitch black sky
荒々しく引き千切って
Roughly tearing it apart
ほらその場所で 聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
Look, in that place, you can hear the heartbeat's mechanism
轟くのは己の調べ
What roars is your own melody
誰かのじゃない己の調べ
Not someone else's, your own melody
目の前に広がる
Spreading out before my eyes
世界はブルー
The world is blue
ひとまず さあ MOVE MOVE
For now, come on, MOVE MOVE
SPEAK ABOUT 生き方
SPEAK ABOUT way of life
THERE'S NO NEED 何をそんなに
THERE'S NO NEED, why are you...
張り切って偉そうに
...so eager and acting so high and mighty?
GIVE ME MORE 愛を
GIVE ME MORE love
右も左も
Both right and left
知りもしないで笑いだ
Laughing without even knowing
DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
ニヤリ影が笑う
A shadow smirks and laughs
世界は大概
The world is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
繰り返すように RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
Like repeating, RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
わかってはいない
You don't even understand
アレコレ OVERWRITE
This and that OVERWRITE
TELL ME SOMETHING FOR THE NEW
偉大な期待の時代のバイブル
A bible of a great, expectant era
CLAP BACK
LOSIN' MY MIND SHOOTING MY SIDE
SAVE IT あなたのその瞬間
SAVE IT, that moment of yours
MAYBE NOTHING WRONG NOTHING WRONG
LA RI LA LA LA LA RI LA
誰もが大概
Everyone is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON on a momentary emotion
心は 95
The heart is 95
狂気のサムライ
A crazy samurai
血走らせた目で READY TO LIVE READY TO DIE
With bloodshot eyes, READY TO LIVE READY TO DIE
陽は昇り
The sun rises
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
Your sky, a pitch-black sky
あらあらしく引き引きちぎって
Tear it apart roughly
ほらその場所で
Look, in that place
聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
The mechanism of the heartbeats you can hear
驚くのは まだこれから まだこれから
The surprising part is still to come, still to come
WAITING
時計の針 迷宮の街
The hands of the clock, the labyrinth city
猛々しく WITH A RAISE YOUR VOICE
Fiercely, WITH A RAISE YOUR VOICE
ほらすぐそこで 始まり出す孤高の宴
Look, right there, the start of a lonely banquet
奏でるのは己の調べ
What's playing is my own melody
唯一無二の己の調べ
One and only, my own melody
わーい！
Yay!
Perhatian sang putri merak yang tertiup angin. Aku Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID.
Attention, the peacock princess blown by the wind. I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID.
Attention please, I'm Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2!
皆様ごきげんよう、私ホロライブインドネシア二期生パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの！
Greetings everyone, I am Pavolia Reine of Hololive Indonesia's 2nd Generation!
And welcome to Pavolia Reine's Peafowl of the Blue Flame!
Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 Birthday! Welcome!
いぇーい、ようこそ！
Yay, welcome!
えーと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして...
Um, there's a hashtag on the upper left...
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner...
...it reads #ReineMEPtember2025...
...which is the pretty much same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
...which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah?
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything, you can write it...
...and I'll be looking forward to them. ご感想とか色々、皆さんも書くことができます。
...and I'll be looking forward to them. You all can write your thoughts and everything.
チャンプルーな話し方になってますけど。 I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live.
My way of speaking is getting all mixed up. I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live.
You don't have to write it now, 今じゃなくても大丈夫ですけど、but I will be waiting!
You don't have to write it now, it's okay if not right now, but I will be waiting!
Yes, so just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage. Look at this! It's so cool, right?
There's mysterious flames, mysterious locks, mysterious cans, mysterious... where's the liquid?
Well, there was like a blue liquid there, but I mean you saw it, right? Yeah!
If you, um, I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know...
...usually you guys think of the color red, right? Automatically.
そうですね、火といえば赤のイメージが強いかもしれませんが...
That's right, when you think of fire, the image of red might be strong, but...
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Iya kan?
But actually, the blue flame is the strongest. Right?
But actually, 実はですね、青い炎が一番強い。と思います。
But actually, blue flames are the strongest. I think.
Yeah! So that's the theme of today's birthday.
I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through hot songs and songs that will make you feel...
...aduh gerah banget, so atsui, so woosh, gitu. Pokoknya just look forward to it, okay?
...so hot, so hot, so woosh, or something. Anyway, just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs we've sung today, we have two songs.
The first one was "Kill Kiss". すごく好きな曲で、Ave Mujica様の「Kill Kiss」です。
The first one was "Kill Kiss". A song I really like, Ave Mujica's "Kill Kiss".
そして二曲目は、私がすごい大好きなプロセカのユニット、Vivid BAD SQUAD様の「CRZY」でした。
And the second song was "CRZY" by Vivid BAD SQUAD, a unit from ProSekai that I really love.
And the second song was "CRZY" from a unit I really really like from ProSekai, Vivid BAD SQUAD. I hope you guys enjoyed it! Yay!
Emang kayak Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya.
Reine really loves the song.
Jadi masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs and I'm sure there's a lot of guests.
So there's still more to come. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs and I'm sure there's a lot of guests.
I hope you guys are excited for them! これからもね、もっともっと熱くなるから。ゲストも many many many many many...
I hope you guys are excited for them! It's going to get even hotter from here. There are many guests too...
I'm gonna sing
one of my original songs.
Do you guys know what it is?
The next song is:
Love Me Love Me.
Love Me Love Me / Lyrics, Music, Arrangement: YUC'e
ずっと君の隣
Always by your side
じっと
Just
見てるばかり
staring at you
愛 愛
Love, love
止まない雨
unending rain
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in the world
AM 刻むように
Like carving AM
心
Heart
今 この手にと
taking it in this hand now
痛みさえも愛
Even pain is
のかたち
a form of love
運命に
Fate-bound
結ばれた小指握る
pinkies held tight
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
Love me Love me
私しか要らない
I only need myself
Love me Love me
君がいらない
I don't need you
ぎゅっと抱きしめたら
If I hold you tight
きっと
You surely
逃げられない
won't be able to escape
チックタック 針が回る
Tick-tock, the hands turn
世界に二人きり
Just the two of us in the world
Guess Dis 交わすように
As if exchanging guesses and disses
感情
Emotions
押し殺して
stifled
悲鳴さえも愛
Even screams are
のメロディ
a melody of love
運命に
Fate-bound
結ばれた小指握る
pinkies held tight
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise
Love me Love me
私しか要らない
I only need myself
Love me Love me
君がいらない
I don't need you
愛して
Loving
愛され
being loved
離れられない
Inseparable
You and Me
二人きり
Just the two of us
Give me your love
願うほど
The more I wish
滴る赤い色
the more the red drips
何もかも
A love that
全て吸い尽くす愛を
sucks everything dry
もっと
Give me
頂戴
more
私しか要らない
I only need myself
Love me Love me
君がいらない
I don't need you
Love me Love me
ファイアダンス / Lyrics, Music: DECO*27
Fire Dance / Lyrics, Music: DECO*27
ま、こんなもんでいいか
Well, I guess this is good enough
わっさわっさ 闇に宵闇
Swish-swish, evening gloom in the darkness
手抜き 手に入れた無理
Slacking off, impossible things obtained
それを大事にするんなら お前の売り
If you cherish that, it's your selling point
いつか来る 後悔
Regrets that will come someday
消せるか 今の自分次第
Whether you can erase them depends on your current self
やるだけやったね だれかじゃなくて
You did what you could, not for someone else
未来の自分に嫌われないように
So as not to be hated by your future self
ひび割れてしまうのだって
Even if it ends up cracking
目の前を埋める壁だって
Even the wall that blocks your view
買って売るなら それで結構
If you sell it off as you please, that's fine
あとはひたすら前に進むだけ
From here on, just push forward
イェイ 誰に好かれれば満たされる
Yeah, who do you need to be liked by to feel satisfied
ほどに こなした時が
When you've done it to that extent
爽快だろう
It must be exhilarating
また 行けるはず
I should be able to go again
まだ やれるはず
I should still be able to do it
ヤバババマナ
Yaba-ba-ba-mana
ぶちかますバンだ
It's the bang to blast off
さあ 歌え踊れ
Now, sing and dance
騒げ 繋ぎビビッてんのか
Make some noise, are you scared of the connection?
ヤバババマナ
Yaba-ba-ba-mana
ぶっ飛ばせ場外
Blast it out of the park
多分で決めた限界なんて
Limits decided by "maybe"
挑戦以前の調査不足さ
Are just lack of research before the challenge
ババババ そんな感じ
Ba-ba-ba-ba, something like that
ババババ いい子のアンチ
Ba-ba-ba-ba, anti-good-child
心の警句に息を足せショックを
Add breath to the warning in your heart, the shock
音鳴る方へ
Toward where the sound is
ヤバババマナ
Yaba-ba-ba-mana
ぶちかますバンだ
It's the bang to blast off
さあ 歌え踊れ
Now, sing and dance
騒ぎ上がれ バラバラ
Raise a ruckus, falling apart
まだまだメラメラさせな！
Keep it burning on and on!
ガンガン昇る今ならごめん　邪魔させぬ頂上へ
Sorry, I'm rising up fast now
Won't let anyone block my way to the top
何があったって盛れ盛れ　ドンドン進め満てる航海目
No matter what happens, keep flourishing
Keep moving forward, eyes on the full voyage
手にしたタガが本番　手広げて手のひら返しは論外
The limits I've seized are just the start
Expanding my reach, turning back is out of the question
重ねる努力　力強きKO!
Piling up efforts, with a powerful KO!
ヤッパパナバナ　ぶちかますバンだ！
Yappapanabana, it's time to let it rip!
さあ歌え踊れ騒げスカビビ天国さ　ハハッ！
Now sing, dance, and make some noise
This is the Sukabibi paradise, haha!
ヤッパパナバナ　ぶっ飛ばす場外！
Yappapanabana, blast it out of the park!
頭で決めて限界なんて　当然一蹴　ちょっと待って
Deciding limits in your head
Is naturally kicked aside, wait a second
黄色のその感じ
That yellow feeling
いい顔のアンジュ
With a great-looking face
好景気に強奪
Snatching it up in a boom
音の鳴る方へ
Towards where the sound is
ヤッパパナバナ　ぶちかますバンだ！
Yappapanabana, it's time to let it rip!
さあ歌え踊れ騒げあげな
Now sing, dance, and raise your voice
マダ　マダ　マダ　サセナ！
Wait, wait, wait, keep it going!
ヤッパパナバナ　ぶちかますバンだ！
Yappapanabana, it's time to let it rip!
段違いのハイに燃え尽きて灰に
On an unparalleled high, burning down to ashes
なってもサンキューラッキー快便
Even so, thank you, lucky, and feelin' great!
ヤッパパナバナ　かっ飛ばす場外！
Yappapanabana, knock it out of the park!
お利口さんにならなくてパッパパ
Don't need to be a well-behaved kid, pappa-pa
パーッとするパーティー　連発するパレード
A party that's going off, a non-stop parade
黄色のその感じ
That yellow feeling
いい顔のアンジュ
With a great-looking face
好景기에強奪
Snatching it up in a boom
音の鳴る方へ
Towards where the sound is
ヤッパパナバナ　ぶちかますバンだ！
Yappapanabana, it's time to let it rip!
さあ歌え踊れ騒げあげな
Now sing, dance, and raise your voice
マダ　マダ　マダ　サセナ！
Wait, wait, wait, keep it going!
夜の始まりさ　バニーガール誘惑される
It's the start of the night
Being tempted by the bunny girl
言動に弾け飛ぶ　葛藤に愛を乾杯
Bursting with every word and action
A toast to love amidst the conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed
恋の始まりさ　バニーガールだらしねえ顔
It's the start of a romance
Bunny girl with a messy, relaxed face
穿って澄んだ　君の目を離さない
I won't let go of your piercing, clear eyes
さあ刻めステップ刻んで
Come on, carve out the steps, carve them in
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue after coming home from work
私とこのグラスに
Leave it with me and this glass
そう自分好みに着替えて
That's right, change into something you like
世間に対する気持ち
Your feelings toward the world
私に注いでみない？ Oh
Why don't you pour them out to me? Oh
ありきたりなラブソングでも　愛が込められてるの
Even a generic love song
Can be filled with love
それでも汚れるのなんて　君を見ればわかるの
But that it'll still get tarnished
I can tell just by looking at you
下を向く君の目を
Those eyes of yours looking down
無理矢理剥ごうとはしない
I won't try to force them open
だからそんな顔せず手を差し伸べてほら
So don't make that face, look, reach out your hand
夜の始まりさ　バニーガール誘惑される
It's the start of the night
Being tempted by the bunny girl
言動に弾け飛ぶ　葛藤に愛を乾杯
Bursting with every word and action
A toast to love amidst the conflict
伝えられなくても
Even if it can't be conveyed
恋の始まりさ　バニーガールだらしねえ顔
It's the start of a romance
Bunny girl with a messy, relaxed face
穿って澄んだ　君の目を離さない
I won't let go of your piercing, clear eyes
君の愛を知った気で　ハイになっていて
Thinking I've known your love, getting high on it
感動去っていて　毎晩泣いていてさ
The emotion has faded, and I'm crying every night
それくらいがいいんでしょ
That's just about right, isn't it?
さあ刻めステップ刻んで
Come on, carve out the steps, carve them in
君の顔色今では　マシになってきてるから
Because your complexion is looking
A bit better now
私をあげるわ　バニーガール誘惑される
I'll give you myself
Being tempted by the bunny girl
言動に弾け飛ぶ　葛藤に愛を乾杯
Bursting with every word and action
A toast to love amidst the conflict
伝えられてるはず
It should be conveyed by now
夜の始まりさ　バニーガールだらしねえ顔
It's the start of the night
Bunny girl with a messy, relaxed face
穿って澄んだ　君の目を離さない
I won't let go of your piercing, clear eyes
ヤムヤムヤミドゥ　ヤムヤムヤミドゥ　ヤムヤムヤミドゥ
Yamyam Yummy Do, Yamyam Yummy Do, Yamyam Yummy Do
あ、星のしんしん　なだれ　徘徊　曖昧　シャットダウン
Ah, star's twinkling, avalanche, wandering, ambiguity, shutdown
幻想のランウェイ　見えきれワンダー
Illusory runway, unseen wonder
急性喪失感だら　アイバ　ムービン　トゥ　サンタキシ
Acute loss feeling, I've been moving to some taxi
引力のダーウィンさ　パッパッパッパラ　まぶす　マイ　ハーツ
Darwin of gravity, pa pa pa para, sprinkle my hearts
諸行無常　クラップス　イット　アップ　デクラレ　ソリューション　クラップス　イット　アップ
All things are impermanent, clap it up, declare solution, clap it up
...イズント　イット　ワース　イット　ワンチャン　狙う　ジャックポット
...isn't it worth it? A one-shot chance, aiming for the jackpot
あ、ズキズキ　パラパ　冷めないうちに
Ah, throbbing parapa, before it cools down
ヤムヤムヤミドゥ　ヤムヤムヤミドゥ
Yamyam Yummy Do, Yamyam Yummy Do
あ、ズキズキ　パラパ　味わい尽くそう
Ah, throbbing parapa, let's savor it all
あ、足りない　まだ足りないな
Ah, it's not enough, it's still not enough
右左　最高　一体　ご馳走様
Left, right, the best, collectively, thanks for the feast
嗜好のメリーアジュ　駆け足　ルメスピ
Preferred marriage, dashing lumispi
右か左か　逃げる　真っ先だ
Right or left, run away first
ドッチュドッチュダッタカ　乱気流　ダンスホール
Docchu docchu dattaka, turbulent dancehall
たまごのうさぎだ　フェイスは揃った
It's an egg rabbit, the faces are all here
さぁ　ベイビー　ベイビー　ベイビー　もう時間　フガナイワ
Now, baby baby baby, time is already running out
ヤミヤミヤミ　ヤミヤミヤミ
Yummy yummy yummy, yummy yummy yummy
ラリルララルリ　歪まえてルルラ
Rarirurararuri, distorting rurura
壊れる前に！
Before it breaks!
あ、ドキドキ　パラパ　ルージュを点けて
Ah, thumping parapa, put on some rouge
ヤムヤムヤミドゥ　ヤムヤムヤミドゥ
Yamyam Yummy Do, Yamyam Yummy Do
あ、ドキドキ　パラパ　至福の　リズムで
Ah, thumping parapa, with a blissful rhythm
あ、足りない　まだ足りないわ
Ah, it's not enough, it's still not enough
あ、大概　もう気安いな
Ah, mostly, it's already familiar
こっち向いて　ハニー　充
Look this way, honey, full
痛いことは　嫌いですが
I dislike painful things
君の手のひらは　嫌いじゃない
But I don't dislike your palms
言葉は飴玉みたいに
Words are like candies
甘く広がって　心満たす
Spreading sweetly and filling my heart
あぁ　全然わかってない
Ah, you don't understand at all
永遠に言う通り
Always doing as you say
完全に見えてない
Completely invisible
どこにいても
No matter where I am
あぁ　何で聞いてない
Ah, why aren't you listening?
元々あの子みたいに可愛くならなくちゃ
I have to become cute like that girl from the start
愛は　ショウ　メニー
Love is so many
底は　ハウ　メニー
The bottom is how many
もう大体　何もかも分からなくなる
Already, I almost can't understand anything anymore
曖昧　また　度々
Ambiguity, again, frequently
醜い　ご褒美
Ugly reward
もう　嫌になって　忘れないように
Already getting fed up, so as not to forget
今日だって　ちゃんとな　内緒の　傷繕い
Even today, properly, patching up the secret wounds
ニャンだよ　恋するから
What is it, because I'm in love
愛して
Love me
Everybody today is a loving day.
Get it get it this is my courtship.
Any any any time is fun with me.
Give me give me love me my darling.
愛は間違いなんてみんなは言う
Everyone says love is a mistake
取り憑かれているって
That I'm possessed
ならこの胸で　美しく
Then what is this tightness in my chest
締め付けるような　切なさ　何だろう
A beautiful, agonizing sorrow?
選ぶ言葉と　惑う指先
Chosen words and hesitant fingertips
端正な横顔
A well-formed profile
私しか知らない
Only I know
わがまま　不機嫌も
Selfishness and bad moods too
もしかして今日は　優しくなでてくれるのかな
Maybe you'll stroke me gently today?
君のそれで　耐えられるの
Can I endure it with yours?
生涯で私だけなんだよね
I'm the only one in your life, right?
あからさまに　体　正に
Obviously, my body, truly
もうヤダって離れられないよね
Even if I say I hate it, I can't leave, right?
そうだよね
That's right
感情は徐々に
Emotions are gradually
不体裁は　少々に
The unseemliness, just a bit
もう　愛も罪もよ
Already love and sin too
いつでもいい 柑橘の匂い
Anytime is fine, with the scent of citrus
だって偲ぶのだもん
Because I'm reminiscing
この手叱られるだけだし
This hand will just get scolded anyway
今日だってちゃんとお膝でおとなしく
Even today, I'll be well-behaved on your lap
にゃんてお好きなように
Nya, just as you like
風情を出して
With a bit of style
「はい喜んで」
"Yes, with pleasure"
「あなた方のため」
"For the sake of you all"
「はい謹んで」
"Yes, with respect"
「あなた方のため」
"For the sake of you all"
差し伸びてきた手
A hand reached out
さながら正義仕立て
As if tailored by justice
嫌々で生き延びて
Surviving reluctantly
わからずやに盾
A shield for the stubborn
「はい喜んで あなた方のために」
"Yes, with pleasure, for your sake"
「出来ることなら出来るとこまで」
"If possible, as far as I can go"
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
奈落音頭奏でろ ドンドン
Play the Hell Dance Song, don-don
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
鳴らせ君の3~6マス トントントツツトトトントン
Sound your 3 to 6 squares, ton-ton-ton-tsu-tsu-to-to-ton-ton
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Dance)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Sound it more)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Dance)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Sound it more)
慣らせ君の病の町を ドンドン
Get used to your diseased town, don-don
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドンドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, don-don
うっちゃれ 正義の超人たちを ドンドン
Cast aside the superhumans of justice, don-don
鳴らせ君の3~6マス トントントツツトトトントン
Sound your 3 to 6 squares, ton-ton-ton-tsu-tsu-to-to-ton-ton
怒り抱いても 勝つ優しさが勝つ
Even if you hold anger, winning kindness will win
あなたの欠けたとこが希望
Your missing parts are hope
Save this game, Mr. A.
救われたのは僕のうちの一人で
I was one of those who were saved
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
奈落音頭奏でろ ドンドン
Play the Hell Dance Song, don-don
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward
嫌なこと思い出して
Remember the unpleasant things
鳴らせ君の3~6マス
Sound your 3 to 6 squares
分かれ道思うがまま Go To Earth
At the crossroads, follow your heart, Go To Earth
任せたきりワガママな言葉
Selfish words left behind
奏でるハクナマタタの音は トントントツツトトトントン
The Hakuna Matata sound playing is ton-ton-ton-tsu-tsu-to-to-ton-ton
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Dance)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Sound it more)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (踊れ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Dance)
ギリギリダンス ギリギリダンス (もっと鳴らせ)
Giri-giri dance, giri-giri dance (Sound it more)
慣らせ君の病の町を ドンドン
Get used to your diseased town, don-don
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン ドンドン
Hide the laughable opinions of others, don-don
うっちゃれ 正義の超人たちを ドンドン
Cast aside the superhumans of justice, don-don
鳴らせ君の3~6マス トントントツツトトトントン
Sound your 3 to 6 squares, ton-ton-ton-tsu-tsu-to-to-ton-ton
はい喜んで あなた方のために
Yes, with pleasure, for your sake
出来ることなら出来るとこまで
If possible, as far as I can go
はい謹んで あなた方のために
Yes, with respect, for your sake
鳴らせ君の3~6マス トントントツツトトトントン
Sound your 3 to 6 squares, ton-ton-ton-tsu-tsu-to-to-ton-ton
（叫び声）
(Shouting)
アニポチママ！
Anya-poci-mama!
読者の皆様、こんにちは。お疲れ様です、アーニャ・メルフィッサです。イェーイ！
Hello readers, good afternoon. I'm Anya Melfissa. Yay!
あ、あー、ママが教えてもらった言葉で
Ah, with the words Mama taught me...
お嬢様言葉で自己紹介します。
I'll introduce myself in lady-like language.
皆様ごきげんよう。わたくし、パヴォリア・レイネ... あ、すいません。
Everyone, good day. I am Pavolia Reine... ah, sorry.
ごきげんよう、リサとリサと...
Good day, Risa and Risa...
ごきげんよう、わたくし、ホロライブインドネシア2期生パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。以後お見知りおきを！
Good day, I am Pavolia Reine, Hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen. Pleased to make your acquaintance!
本物のお嬢様でございますね。イェーイ！
A real lady indeed. Yay!
お嬢様です。完全に。
A lady indeed. Completely.
お嬢様配信！
Lady stream!
お嬢様ムービング！
Lady moving!
Yes, お嬢様ムービング。
Yes, lady moving.
（歓声）
(Cheers)
レイネちゃん。
Reine-chan.
Selamat ulang tahun.
Happy birthday.
Terima kasih! Happy birthday!
Thank you! Happy birthday!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
さっきはバリガールを一緒に歌いました！
Earlier, we sang 'Bari Girl' together!
いかがでしたでしょうか？
How was it?
どうだった？ 踊れてた？
How was it? Was I dancing well?
ナイス！
Nice!
もう腰が...
My lower back is already...
ノー！ マッサージ、マッサージ。
No! Massage, massage.
肩、肩お願いします。肩。
Shoulders, shoulders please. Shoulders.
ありがとうございます。これこれ。
Thank you very much. This is it.
わたくしもマッサージがほしい！
I want a massage too!
はい。お客様凝ってますね。ここですか？ こちらですか？
Yes. Customer, you're quite stiff. Is it here? Is it this way?
（叫び声）
(Shouting)
パーフェクトでございます。
It's perfect.
パーフェクト！
Perfect!
Pochi-mama and Reine!
No Bunny Girl!
お父様ハイテンションで今日もお素晴らしいです。
My lady, you're high tension and wonderful today as well.
さすがです。
As expected.
Hari ini, today...
Today, today...
...apa ya, gimana ngomongnya.
...how should I put it.
Pochi-mama, did you guys see last time
Pochi-mama's 3D ohirome?
Pochi-mama's 3D debut?
そう、二人でわたくしの3Dお披露目で...
Yes, for my 3D debut, the two of us...
...レイネちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました。皆様見ていただけましたでしょうか？
...sang and danced together. Did everyone see it?
And because of that, today, I invited Pochi-mama...
...to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
Yay, thank you so much for inviting, Reine!
Yay, thank you so much for inviting me, Reine!
Arigato!
Thank you!
No thank you, thank you for coming. I had so much fun!
Jadi, apa ya, ngomongin apa ya?
So, what should we talk about?
What should we talk about?
If I remember Pochi-mama, I remember Ojou-sama.
If I remember Pochi-mama, I remember "The Lady".
Because back then, I thought...
...ya gimana ya, I'm a princess.
...well, I'm a princess.
So I have to act like a princess.
お嬢様だからあの日本語で...
Because I'm a lady, in Japanese...
...apa sih? Ojou-sama. Ya Ojou-sama acting hitsuyo hitsuyo gitu guys.
...what is it? Lady. Yeah, lady acting is necessary, guys.
もう、これでパーフェクトです。さっきの動きで。
That was already perfect. That movement just now.
さっきのジャンプで。
With that jump.
OKです。こっちの動きで。
OK. With this movement.
こっちで。こっちでお嬢様。
With this. With this, a lady.
これがホロライブIDお嬢様。
This is the Hololive ID Lady.
皆様もお嬢様になりたい方はね、ちょっとしてください。
Everyone who wants to be a lady, please 'follow'.
「ちょっとしてください」って何ですか？
What do you mean by 'follow'?
Contoh apa?
Follow what?
真似してください！
Please imitate me!
そう、こんな動きがお嬢様ですよ！うわーお！
Yes, these movements are lady-like! Whoa!
本当にいいんですかね、これで。
Is this really okay?
ちなみに、あのネタバレになると思うんですが...
By the way, I think this might be a spoiler...
...あの今日のグッズはね、誕生日グッズはね...
...today's goods, the birthday goods...
...Pochi-mamaが頑張りました！Yay!
...Pochi-mama worked hard on them! Yay!
描かせていただきました！皆様...
I was allowed to draw them! Everyone...
...ちゃんとグッズ紹介まで最後までしっかり見てくださいね。よろしくお願いいたします。
...please watch until the end for the goods intro. Thank you.
Pokoknya katanya jangan ke mana-mana guys.
Anyway, she says don't go anywhere, guys.
Pokoknya tunggu sampai akhir karena ada goods dari Pochi-mama sensei.
Wait until the end for the goods from Pochi-mama sensei.
Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan kan? Makanya...
You don't want to miss it, right? So...
...tonton sampai habis. OK?
...watch until the end. OK?
Thank you Pochi-mama for coming!
Arigato! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
このあともライブが続くので...
The live will continue after this, so...
...楽しんでね！Yay!
...enjoy! Yay!
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai ♡ Scream!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you
tell me mo mo mo tell me mo mo mo
聴かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice
let me hear mo mo mo let me hear mo mo mo
こんなときドキ もう耐えきれない
At a time like this, I can't take it anymore
oh I need you oh oh I need you
戸惑い卒教 運命の私に
Graduating from hesitation, to my destined self
続けてほしいの
I want you to continue
勇気を出して
Have some courage
見つめる作戦
The staring strategy
瞳が合えば
If our eyes meet
Yay yay yay
この恋 この愛で
With this love, with this affection
目眩めき 溶けちゃうよ
Dazzling and melting away
ねえ ねえ ねえ 気づいて my darling
Hey hey hey, notice me my darling
とろける 大好き
Melting, I love you
レディちゃん、ハイ！
Redi-chan, yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミン党！よりもあなた！
Chocomint party! More than that, you!
アユムちゃん、ハイ！
Ayumu-chan, yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバー！よりもあなた！
Strawberry flavor! More than that, you!
シキちゃん、ハイ！
Shiki-chan, yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー&クリーム！よりもあなた！
Cookies & cream! More than that, you!
みんな、ハイ！
Everyone, yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き、アイスクリーム！
Of course, I love it, ice cream!
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah, yeah, yeah! この恋、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this love, with this affection...
メンメンピッと溶けちゃうよ
I'm melting away!
ねえねえねえ 気づいてマイダーリン
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling.
とろけ、大好き
I'm melting, I love you.
お願い見つけてマイダーリン
Please find me, my darling.
お願い気づいてマイダーリン
Please notice me, my darling.
勇気を出して
Work up the courage.
近づく作戦
Strategy to get closer.
手と手が触れて
Hand in hand, touching.
止められない
I can't stop.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! この恋、この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah! With this love, with this affection...
メンメンピッと溶けちゃうよ
I'm melting away!
ねえねえねえ 気づいてマイダーリン
Hey, hey, hey, notice me, my darling.
それは あなた
It's you.
Please don't say you are lazy
だって 本当は crazy
Because the truth is, I'm crazy.
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Swans, you see, are paddling their feet where they can't be seen.
本能に忠実 忠実 翻弄も重々承知
Faithful to instinct, and well aware of being toyed with.
前途洋々だし だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
The future is bright, so I take a break once in a while.
黒目で見つめられたら 行き先 秩序も真っ白
When you stare at me with those dark eyes, my destination and order turn pure white.
近道あればそれが王道 省ける翼もあれば上等
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road; it's fine if I have wings I can save.
ヤバ 爪割れた ぐるぐる補修した
Oh no, I broke a nail; I patched it up all over.
それだけでなんか達成感 大事なのは自分可愛がること
Just that gives me a sense of accomplishment. The important thing is to be kind to yourself.
自分を愛さなきゃ他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others.
Please don't say you are lazy
だって 本当は crazy
Because the truth is, I'm crazy.
能ある鷹はそう 見えないとこにピック隠すんです
A wise hawk, you see, hides its pick where it can't be seen.
想像に一生懸命 現実は絶体絶命
Working hard on imagination, reality is a desperate situation.
発展途上だし だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
I'm still a work in progress, so I occasionally go out of pitch.
その目に映らないだけだって やる気はメーター振り切っていて
Just because you can't see it in your eyes, my motivation is off the charts.
いつでも全力で夢見て その分全力で眠って
Always dreaming with all my might, and sleeping with all my might as well.
やべぇ 痩せすぎた 調整して食った
Oh man, I lost too much weight; I adjusted by eating.
それだけでなんか敗北感 次なる目標を上方修正して
Just that gives me a sense of defeat. I'll revise my next goal upwards.
柔軟に臨機応変千変万化
Flexible and adaptable, ever-changing.
Please don't say you are lazy
だって 本当は crazy
Because the truth is, I'm crazy.
孔雀たちはそう
Peafowls, you see...
アッと言う間に一周です
In the blink of an eye, a whole round is done
要素は満身創痍
The elements are battered and bruised
願望は粗食ベイジン
Desires are a plain diet
誘惑は発酵食品
Temptations are fermented food
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
That's why my will is so easily broken
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
やっぱまさかウェットポイント
As I thought, unexpectedly, a wet point
いじりくり回して
Fiddling with it over and over
それだけでペンタゴンズはもう空
Just with that, the Pentagons are already empty
大事なのは自分
The important thing is to accept yourself
認めていくこと
Accept yourself
自分を許さなきゃ
If you don't forgive yourself
他人も許せない
You can't forgive others
Please don't say you are lazy
だって本当はcrazy
Because in reality, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう
Swans are like that
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Kicking their feet where they can't be seen
本能に従順忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct
翻弄も重々承知
Well aware of being tossed about
前途洋々だーし
The future is bright
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
That's why I take a break sometimes
Wah! Gimana? How was it?
Wah! How was it? How was it?
Wasn't the gondola and the bazooka and everything very cool?
We've sung so many songs,
but there's still more!
Here's the long-awaited...
Goods introduction!
今回は生誕グッズがありまーす！
This time we have birthday goods!
Yeah!
まずはこちらですね、
First is this one,
青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット。
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat.
Ini seperti dijanjikan ya,
This is as promised,
just like how we said earlier,
totally not a spoiler, made by Pochi-mama!
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mat/desk mat,
and so we have another one!
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat,
well, ini ada lagi.
well, here's another one.
Beda. It's different.
It's different. It's different.
It's different! Yay!
And along with the rubber mat,
we have the tapestry!
Yay!
Ini kalian tidak tergoreng ya,
You won't get burned by this,
ya nggak apa-apa lah kegoreng dikit pokoknya keren.
it's okay to get burned a bit, anyway it's cool.
Yes, sesuai tema live dari kali ini,
Yes, in accordance with the theme of this live,
we have...
青い炎の孔雀タペストリー！
Peafowl of the Blue Flame Tapestry!
Gambarnya sama tapi kali ini edisi tapestry ya,
The image is the same but this time it's the tapestry edition,
dibuat oleh Pochi-mama juga.
also made by Pochi-mama.
Silakan dicek out, silakan dicek out.
Please check it out, please check it out.
Dan,
And,
続いてはこちらですね。
next is this one.
Mana nih lanjutannya?
Where's the next part?
Buat kalian yang suka minimalist design,
For those of you who like minimalist design,
for those of you who like designs that are more minimalistic in nature,
we have Blueming Flame Coaster.
咲き誇る青い炎のコースター。
Blooming Blue Flame Coaster.
Yes!
Dan pokoknya temanya itu cocok banget
And anyway, the theme fits perfectly
sama tapestry-nya dan juga rubber mat-nya yang tadi ya,
with the tapestry and the rubber mat from earlier,
ilustrasi Pochi-mama.
Pochi-mama's illustration.
Jadi mendingan
So you'd better
masukkan ke keranjang sekarang juga.
put it in your cart right now.
Eh, belum bisa ya?
Oh, not yet?
Ya udahlah nggak apa-apa.
Well, it's okay.
And then next one,
さらにこちら！
furthermore, this!
Ada juga,
There's also,
いつものようにボイスがあります。
as usual there is a voice pack.
Kali ini karena Reine suka sekali sushi,
This time, because Reine likes sushi very much,
because I love sushi so much, 寿司大好きレイネが
because I love sushi so much, sushi-loving Reine
membuat...
has made...
『シークレット寿司作戦』
"Secret Sushi Strategy"
Voice Pack!
Untuk kalian yang suka sushi juga mungkin ya.
For those of you who like sushi too, maybe.
Let's go!
最後に、フルセットを購入いただいた方には、
Lastly, for those who purchased the full set,
buat yang beli full set akan ada
for those who buy the full set there will be
数量限定で直筆メッセージと
a limited quantity with handwritten message and
箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます！
a foil-stamped replica signed postcard!
Akan ada limited edition postcard
There will be a limited edition postcard
yang ada message dan tanda tangan dari Reine juga.
that has a message and signature from Reine too.
There's gonna be a limited edition postcard...
buat yang beli...
for those who buy...
eh, Indonesia lagi.
oh, Indonesian again.
For those people who buy the full set!
Let's go!
通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入り
The regular version has a foil-stamped replica signature and message
apa tuh? ポストカードがついてきます。
what was it? It comes with a postcard.
Yang beli biasa juga akan ada postcard yang ada message dan sign ya.
Those who buy the regular one will also have a postcard with a message and signature.
Oke.
Okay.
And then next up,
I'm gonna introduce...
my new song!
Never sang in this genre, so I'm a little bit shy.
It's a little bit different from what I usually sing,
so I hope you guys can, gimana ya,
so I hope you guys can, how should I say it,
if it could resonate with you guys even for a little, I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするの初めてでした。
It's the first time I've done a song in this genre.
And...
だからね、ちょっとシャイです。
So, I'm a little shy.
And, yeah, well basically, well,
being placed in a box you don't exactly fit, it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know,
it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you, you.
And even if you're broken, it's fine.
And no one else's opinions should change that.
And, okay.
とにかく、自分をありのままを愛していいよって曲です。
Anyway, it's a song that says it's okay to love yourself as you are.
じゃあ、あの、これから準備するので待っててね。
Well, I'm going to prepare now, so please wait.
Please wait 'cause I'm gonna prepare, I got a surprise!
Yay! Bye-bye!
PAVOLIA REINE MEMBERSHIP PROMOTIONAL VIDEO "The Royaltea"
Attention please!
注目！
Attention!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
新鮮な体験をお求めの方！
For those looking for a fresh experience!
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats,
私が「アレ」を解禁するのを
Waiting for me to unlock "that"
ずっと心待ちにしているMERAKyatsの皆様！
To all MERAKyats who have been waiting patiently!
who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing
そして、ただただ素敵なバッジや絵文字を見せつけて
And, just to show off lovely badges and emojis
周囲にマウントを取りたいあなた！
You, who wants to flex on those around you!
using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
朗報です！
Good news!
My name is Pavolia Reine,
本日は、
Today,
and I'm going to be here explaining briefly
パヴォリア・レイネのメンバーシップについて
about Pavolia Reine's membership
簡単にご紹介いたします
I will briefly introduce it
what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership.
(That's mine, by the way.)
(あ、レイネって私のことです)
(Ah, Reine is me)
At The Royaltea,
our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights,
超級魔法による特製バッジを表示する権利が与えられ
Granted the right to display special badges from grand magic
which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
チャンネル内で周りにアピールできちゃいます
You can appeal to those around you in the channel
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging
それだけでなくご加入者様へのギフトとして
Not only that, as a gift to subscribers
by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
限定モノのカワイイ絵文字もご用意しています
We also have limited edition cute emojis
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties,
ご加入者様だけが参加できる秘密のRoyalteaパーティ
Secret Royaltea party only for members
which also means membership-exclusive streams
つまりメンバーシップ限定配信もございます
Which means there are also membership-only streams
in which we can have various talks, play games together,
雑談に花を咲かせたり一緒にゲームをしたり
Having lively chats or playing games together
and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
他にも様々な企画を予定しています
We also have various other projects planned
Like what, you might ask?
どんな企画か気になるって？
Wondering what kind of projects?
Only one way to find out.
なら、すべきことはお分かりですね
Then, you know what you should do
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed,
なお、安全は保障されておりません これは...
Note: Safety is not guaranteed. This is...
but it is...
...development training in which we aim to build a community
of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
The Royalteaへのご加入を心よりお待ちしています
We look forward to your joining The Royaltea
Wake up another bloody Monday,
say things never wanted to say,
up in arms who can please you live it day by day.
Wake up another bloody Monday,
rinse and repeat until it's Sunday,
hold it so frustrated you know I can't do it no more.
I'll say,
no good down to the core here you go knocking
beating down my door.
Yell out scream and shout
but I'll never change it now,
I'm just too much but not enough to please your right.
Your idea of ideal that you're screaming in my hair,
I'm just so broken.
I'll stop me,
or never figure it out.
Never never never gonna figure it out.
You want me to know what I just don't know,
put me in a hurry in a hymn or low,
little that you know I'm just me let it go,
lock me inside a thing of your perfection correction.
Tear me down am I what you like now,
don't tell me what to do what to say what to,
think about everything that you ever said.
I'll say,
goodness being so bad what's the issue
I'll screw up again.
Yell out scream and shout
but I'll never change it now,
I'm just too much but not enough to please your right.
Your idea of ideal that you're screaming in my hair,
I'm just so broken.
...so broken, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Comfortable and pathetic
I like it that way, get it?
The brittle, the settle
Is never that simple
But I so want to meet your heart criteria
Too bad that I'm never gonna
I'm never gonna fit
How now?
One, two!
Yeah, I'll laugh, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much but not enough
To please your eye
Your idea of ideal
That you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken, yeah
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Hey!
I'll stop me
I'll never figure it out
Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out
Figure it out
Hey!
I'll never gonna figure it out
PAVOLIA REINE ORIGINAL SONG
Figure it Out
SONG & MV COMING SOON